Photograph File (Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum Records--Curatorial Division) RG.0008
Library and Archives
Photograph File (Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum Records--Curatorial Division)
1923-2006, undated
RG.0008
Library and Archives
20.0 Linear feet (7 file cabinet drawers, 2 oversize boxes)
The Photograph File for the Curatorial Division of the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum consists of approximately 1,500 artist files, as well as files dedicated to specific locations, photographers, subjects, and exhibits. The bulk of the artist files consists of photocopies of images from Corbis, Getty, and the Michael Ochs Archives that include information on obtaining permission for the use of those images. Some of the artist files also contain original publicity stills, performance shots, negatives, and slides. These files were originally compiled by the Curatorial Department for reference in curating exhibits, but have also been used across the institution for development, marketing, publications, research, and other purposes as copyright allows. Also included in the collection are files of images with unidentified people and places, and subject-based folders containing images relevant to the work of the Curatorial Division (i.e., Artists and motorcycles). Researchers may want to view these files if a desired artist’s name is not found to be listed individually. There are also files containing the work of individual photographers; this material was originally filed at the end of the collection but is now filed alphabetically with the rest of the collection materials.
Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum. Curatorial Division
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Patrons must sign the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibilities and Privacy Rights statement on the Researcher Registration form before using this collection. Consult the Library and Archives in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
Accruals
Accruals are ongoing. They are interfiled with the collection upon receipt.
Custodial History
The Photograph File (Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum Records--Curatorial Division) was transferred to the Library and Archives in August of 2010.
Separated Materials
Some items are on exhibit. These items are noted at the file level. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
ABBA (Musical group); AC/DC (Musical group); Ackerman, Paul; Aerosmith (Musical group); Alice Cooper (Musical group); Allman Brothers Band; Allman, Gregg, 1947-; Animals (Musical group).; Anka, Paul; Armstrong, Louis, 1901-1971; Atkins, Chet; Baez, Joan; Baker, LaVern; Ballard, Hank; Band (Musical group); Basie, Count, 1904-1984; Bass, Ralph; Beach Boys; Beastie Boys; Beatles; Beck, Jeff; Bee Gees; Benjamin, Benny, 1925-1969; Berry, Chuck; Black Sabbath (Musical group); Blackwell, Chris, 1937-; Bland, Bobby; Blondie (Musical group); Bo Diddley, 1928-2008; Booker T. & the MG's (Musical group); Bottom Line (Cabaret: New York, N.Y.); Bowie, David; Brown, Charles, 1922-1999; Brown, James, 1933-2006; Brown, Ruth, 1928-2006; Brubeck, Dave; Buckley, Tim, 1947-1975; Buffalo Springfield (Musical group); Burke, Solomon; Burton, James, 1939-; Byrds (Musical group); Cash, Johnny; Charles, Ray, 1930-2004; Cher, 1946-; Chess, Leonard, 1917-1969; Christian, Charlie, 1916-1942; Clapton, Eric; Clark, Dick, 1929-; Clash (Musical group); Cliff, Jimmy; Clinton, George, 1940-; Coasters (Musical group); Cochran, Eddie, 1938-1960; Cocker, Joe; Cohen, Leonard, 1934-; Cole, Nat King, 1919-1965; Collins, Judy, 1939-; Collins, Phil; Cooke, Sam; Costello, Elvis; Cramer, Floyd, 1933-1997; Cream (Musical group); Creedence Clearwater Revival (Musical group); Crickets (Musical group); Crosby, Stills & Nash; Cure (Musical group); Curtis, King, 1934-1971; Daniels, Charlie, 1936-; Darin, Bobby; Dave Clark Five (Musical group).; Davies, Ray, 1944-; Davis, Clive; Davis, Guy, 1952-; Davis, Miles; Dead Boys (Musical group); Dells (Musical Group); Diamond, Neil; Dion, 1939-; Dixon, Willie, 1915-1992; Domino, Fats, 1928-; Donahue, Tom, 1928-1975; Donovan, 1946-; Doors (Musical group); Douglas, Steve, 1938-1993; Dozier, Lamont; Drifters (Musical group); Dylan, Bob, 1941-; Eagles (Musical group); Earth, Wind, and Fire (Musical group); Eddy, Duane; Ertegun, Ahmet M.; Ertegun, Nesuhi; Everly Brothers; Fender, Leo, 1909-1991; Flamingos (Musical group).; Fleetwood Mac (Musical group); Fontana, D.J.; Four Seasons (Musical group).; Four Tops (Musical group); Franklin, Aretha; Freed, Alan; Gamble, Kenny; Gaye, Marvin; Genesis (Musical group); Gladys Knight and the Pips; Goffin, Gerry; Gordy, Berry; Graham, Bill, 1931-1991; Grateful Dead (Musical group); Guns n' Roses (Musical group); Guthrie, Woody, 1912-1967; Guy, Buddy; Haley, Bill, 1925-1981; Hammond, John, 1910-1987; Harrison, George, 1943-2001; Hayes, Isaac; Hendrix, Jimi; Holiday, Billie, 1915-1959; Holland, Brian; Holland, Eddie; Hollies (Musical group); Holly, Buddy, 1936-1959; Holzman, Jac; Hooker, John Lee; Howlin' Wolf, 1910-1976; Huff, Leon; Impressions (Musical group); Ink Spots (Musical group).; Isley Brothers; Jackson 5 (Musical group); Jackson, Mahalia, 1911-1972; Jackson, Michael, 1958-2009; Jackson, Wanda, 1937-; Jamerson, James, 1936-1983; James, Elmore, 1918-1963; Jefferson Airplane (Musical group); Joel, Billy; John, Dr., 1941-; John, Elton; John, Little Willie, 1937-1968; Johns, Glyn; Johnson, Johnnie, 1924-2005; Johnson, Robert, 1911-1938; Joplin, Janis; Jordan, Louis, 1908-1975; King, B.B.; Kinks (Musical group); Kirshner, Don; Leadbelly, 1885-1949; Led Zeppelin (Musical group); Lee, Brenda, 1944-; Leiber, Jerry; Lennon, John, 1940-1980; Lewis, Jerry Lee; Little Anthony & the Imperials; Little Richard, 1932-; Little Walter, 1930-1968; Love, Darlene; Lovin' Spoonful (Musical group); Lymon, Frankie; Lynyrd Skynyrd (Musical group); Madonna, 1958-; Mamas and the Papas (Musical group); Marley, Bob; Martha and the Vandellas (Musical group); Martin, George, 1926-; Mayfield, Curtis; McCartney, Paul; McPhatter, Clyde; Mellencamp, John, 1951-; Metallica (Musical group); Midnighters (Musical group); Miracles (Musical group).; Mitchell, Joni; Monroe, Bill, 1911-1996; Moonglows (Musical group).; Moore, Scotty; Morrison, Van, 1945-; Morton, Jelly Roll, d. 1941; Muddy Waters, 1915-1983; Nathan, Syd, 1904-1968; Nelson, Rick, 1940-1985; Nyro, Laura; O'Jays (Musical group); Orioles (Musical group); Ostin, Mo, 1927-; Otis, Johnny, 1921-; Parliament (Musical group); Paul, Les; Perkins, Carl, 1932-1998; Petty, Tom; Phillips, Sam, 1923-2003; Pickett, Wilson; Pink Floyd (Musical group); Pitney, Gene; Platters (Musical group); Police (Musical group); Pomus, Doc, 1925-1991; Pop, Iggy, 1947-; Presley, Elvis, 1935-1977; Pretenders (Musical group); Price, Lloyd; Prince; Professor Longhair, 1918-1980; Queen (Musical group); R.E.M. (Musical group); Rainey, Ma, 1886-1939; Raitt, Bonnie; Ramones (Musical group); Red Hot Chili Peppers (Musical group); Redding, Otis, d. 1967; Reed, Jimmy, 1925-1976; Righteous Brothers.; Robinson, Smokey, 1940-; Rodgers, Jimmie, 1897-1933; Rolling Stones; Ronettes (Musical group).; Run-D.M.C. (Musical group); Rupe, Art, 1917-; Russell, Leon; Sam & Dave.; Santana (Musical group); Seeger, Pete, 1919-; Seger, Bob; Sex Pistols (Musical group); Shannon, Del; Shirelles (Musical group); Shuman, Mort; Simon and Garfunkel; Simon, Paul, 1941-; Sledge, Percy; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group); Small Faces (Musical group); Smith, Bessie, 1894-1937; Smith, Patti; Sonny & Cher; Soul Stirrers (Musical group); Spector, Phil, 1940-; Springfield, Dusty; Springsteen, Bruce; Staple Singers; Steely Dan (Musical group); Stein, Seymour, 1942-; Stewart, Jim, 1930-; Stewart, Rod; Stoller, Mike; Stone, Jesse; Stooges (Musical group); Supremes (Musical group); Talking Heads (Musical group); Taylor, James, 1948-; Temptations (Musical group); Toussaint, Allen; Traffic (Musical group); Turner, Ike; Turner, Joe, 1911-1985; Turner, Tina; U2 (Musical group); Valens, Ritchie, 1941-1959; Van Halen (Musical group); Velvet Underground (Musical group).; Ventures (Musical group).; Vincent, Gene, 1935-1971; Waits, Tom, 1949-; Walker, T-Bone, 1910-1975; Washington, Dinah, 1924-1963; Wenner, Jann; Wexler, Jerry; Who (Musical group); Williams, Hank, 1972-; Wills, Bob, 1905-1975; Wilson, Jackie; Womack, Bobby; Wonder, Stevie; Yancey, Jimmy, 1898-1951; Yardbirds (Musical group); Young Rascals (Musical group).; Young, Neil, 1945-; Zappa, Frank; ZZ Top (Musical group); Boy bands; Folk musicians; Girl groups (Musical groups); Guitarists; Negatives (photographic); Photographs; Radio personalities; Rap musicians; Rock groups; Rock musicians; Slides (Photography); Teenage musicians; Women musicians
- 2 Live Crew, undated
- 4 Hero, 1997
- 12 Rounds, 1998
- 98 Degrees, 1999-2000
- 311, 1998
- 10,000 Maniacs, undated
- A1, 2002
- Abandoned Pools, undated
- Abba, undated
- Accept, undated
- AC/DC, undated
- Ackerman, Paul, circa 1954
- Adams, Bryan, 1993, undated
- Aerosmith, 1978, 2001, undated
- Afghan Whigs, 1993, 1996
- Aguilera, Christina, 2000-2001
- Akron Art Museum, Arthur Fellig exhibit, 2001
- Alabama, undated
- Alexander, Arthur, 1994, undated
- Alice in Chains, 1995
- Alien Ant Farm, 2001
- Allen, Hoss, undated
- Allen, Vernie, undated
- Allison, Mose, 1960, undated
- Allman Brothers, 1970, undated
- Allsup, Tommy, undated
- Altered Images, undated
- America, undated
- Amos, Tori, undated
- ...And You Will Know Us By the Trail of Dead, 2002
- Andreone, Leah, undated
- Angels, undated
- Animals, undated (Box OS2, Folder 1, Object 1)
- Anka, Paul, 1956-1968
- Ant, Adam, undated
- Anthony, Marc, undated
- Anthrax, 1993
- Apex Theory, 2001-2002
- Apocalyptica, 1998
- Armstrong, Louis, undated
- Arrested Development, undated
- Artists and motorcycles, 1958-2001
- Athenaeum, undated
- Atkins, Chet, 1945-1985
- Atkins, Roy, 1934
- Audiovent, undated
- Avalon, Frankie, 1955-1968, undated
- Ayler, Albert (Holy Ghost), 1966
- B-52's, undated
- BBMak, undated
- Babyface, undated
- Bachman Turner Overdrive (BTO), undated
- Backstreet Boys, 1999
- Bad Company, undated
- Bad Finger, undated
- Bad Lands, undated
- Badly Drawn Boy, 2002
- Bad Ronald, 2001
- Baez, Joan, undated
- Bailey, Mildred, 1950, undated
- Baio, Scott, 1978-1985
- Baker, Anita, undated
- Baker, LaVern, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 1)
- Ballard, Hank, undated
- The Band, 1993-1995, undated
- Bangles, 1987, undated
- Barenaked Ladies, 2001, undated
- Bar-Kays, undated
- Barry, Len, undated
- Bartholomew, Dave, undated
- Basie, Count, 1957, undated
- Bass, Ralph, undated
- Beach Boys, 1964-1979, undated
- Beastie Boys, undated
- Beatles (2 folders), 1960-1964, undated
- Beau Brummels, undated
- Beautiful Creatures, 2001
- Beautiful South, undated
- Beck, Jeff, undated
- Bee Gees, 1969, undated
- Belfegore, 1984
- Belle, Regina, undated
- Belly, undated
- Benatar, Pat, undated
- Benjamin, Benny, undated
- Bennett, Tony, undated
- Benson, George, undated
- Benton, Brook, undated
- Berry, Chuck, undated
  Separated Materials
  Two photographs on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
- Better Than Ezra, undated
- Big Bopper, undated
- Big Maybelle, undated
- Big Star, undated
- Bigdumbface, 2001
- Bilal, 2000
- Bionic Jive, 2001
- Bjork, undated
- Black Crowes, undated
- Black Eyed Peas, 1998
- Black, Frank, 1994
- Black Sabbath, undated
- Black Velvet Band, 1992
- Blackwell, Chris, undated
- Blancmange, undated
- Bland, Bobby, undated
- Bleach, undated
- Blind Faith, 1969, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 2)
- Blind Melon, 1994
- Blink-182, undated
- Blondie, circa 1975
- Blood Brothers, 2002
- Blood, Sweat and Tears, 1968, undated
- Bloomfield, Mike, undated
- Blue Cheer, undated
- Blue Oyster Cult, undated
- Blues Project, undated
- Blues Traveler, 2001
- Blunt, James, undated
- BMI artists, undated
- Bo Diddley, undated (Box OS1, Folder 9, Object 1)
- Bobbettes, undated
- Bon Jovi, Jon, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 3)
- Bonds, Gary U.S., undated
- Bongos, undated
- Bonney, Simon, undated
- Book of Love, 2001
- Booker T and the MG's, 1967, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 4)
- Boone, Pat, 1955-1966, undated
- Bostic, Earl, undated
- Boston, undated
- Botti, Chris, 2001
- Bottom Line Club (New York, N.Y.), undated
- Bow Wow Wow, circa 1981-1982
- Bowie, David, 1976-1996, undated (Box OS2, Folder 1, Object 5)
- Box of Frogs, undated
- Box Tops, undated
- Boy George, undated
- Boyce, Tommy and Bobby Hart, undated
- Boyz II Men, undated
- Boyzone, undated
- Bradford, Professor Alex, undated
- Brady Bunch, 1969-1975
- Brand Nubian, 1992
- Brandy, undated
- Braxton, Toni, undated
- Breeders, 1993
- Brewer and Shipley, undated
- Broken English, undated
- Brooks, Donnie, 1993
- Broonzy, Big Bill, undated
- Brother, 2000-2001
- Brother Phelps, undated
- Brown, Arthur (Crazy World of Arthur Brown), undated
- Brown, Charles, undated
- Brown, Clarence "Gatemouth", undated
- Brown, James, 1968-2006, undated (Box OS1, Folder 1, Folder 9, Object 2)
- Brown, Roy, undated
- Brown, Ruth, undated
- Browne, Jackson, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 5)
- Brubeck, Dave, undated
- Bryson, Peabo, undated
- Buckcherry, undated
- Buckley, Jeff, 1993, undated
- Buckley, Tim, undated
- Buffalo Springfield, undated
- Buffett, Jimmy, undated
- Burdon, Eric, undated
- Burdon, Eric, and Brian Auger, undated
- Burgess, Sonny (and the Pacers), undated
- Burke, Solomon, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 6)
- Burnette, Dorsey, undated
- Burnette, Johnny, undated
- Burns, Ken, undated
- Burrell, Kenny, undated
- Burton, James, 1957
- Bush, 1997
- Butterfield, Paul, undated
- Buzzcocks, undated
- BWB, 2002
- Byrds, undated
- Byrne, David, 1997, undated
- Caballe, Montserrat, undated
- Cadillacs, undated
- Cake, 1998-1999
- Campbell, John, 1993
- Can, undated
- Candy Butchers, undated
- Canned Heat, undated
- Cardigans, 1998
- Cardinals
- Carlton, Larry, 2001
- Captain Beefheart, undated
- Carmichael, Hoagy, undated
- Carr, Leroy, undated
- Carroll, Jim, 1998
- Cars, undated
- Carter, Clarence, undated
- Carter Family, undated
- Casady, Jack, undated
- Case, Peter, undated
- Cash, Johnny, 1959-2002, undated
- Cassidy, David, 1972-1987, undated
- Cassidy, Shaun, 1976
- Catharine Wheel, 1997
- Cave, Nick, 2000, undated
- Cellos, undated
- Champion, undated
- Chantals, undated
- Chantays, 1996, undated
- Chapin, Harry, undated
- Chapman, Beth Nielsen, 1997, undated
- Chapman, Tracy, undated
- Charlatans, undated
- Charlatans UK, undated
- Charles, Ray, 1957-2004, undated (Box OS1, Folder 2)
- Charms, undated
- Cheap Trick, 1998, undated
- Checker, Chubby, undated
- Chess, Leonard, undated
- Chesterfield Kings, undated
- Chic, undated
- Chicago, 1984-1997
- Chico and Coolwadda, undated
- Chiffons, undated
- Chilton, Alex, undated
- China Crisis, undated
- Chris and the Sundowners, undated
- Christian, Charlie, undated
- Christy, June, undated
- Christy, Lauren, 1997
- Chuck D, 1998
- Church, Charlotte, 2001
- Citizen Cope, 2001
- City Boy, undated
- City High, 2000
- Clancy Brothers, 1963
- Clannad, undated
- Clapton, Eric, undated
- Clark, Dick, circa 1954-1964, 1996-1997
- Clash (2 folders), 1977-2002
- Classic Example, 1992
- Clayton-Felt, Josh, 2001
- Cleftones, undated
- Clegg, Johnny, 1988
- Cliff, Jimmy, undated
- Cline, Patsy, undated
- Clinton, George, and Parliament-Funkadelic, undated
- Clooney, Rosemary, undated
- Clovers, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 8)
- Coasters, 1955-1957 (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 9)
- Cochran, Eddie, 1958, undated
- Cochrane, Wayne, 1966, undated
- Cocker, Joe, undated
- Cockney Rebel, undated
- Cocteau Twins, 1993
- Cohen, Leonard, 1972-2001, undated
- Cola, 1997
- Cold, undated
- Cole, Natalie, undated
- Cole, Nat King, undated
- Collins, Albert, undated
- Collins, Judy, undated
- Collins, Phil, undated
- Coltrane, John, undated
- Colvin, Shawn, 2001, undated
- Commodores, undated
- Con Funk Shun, undated
- Conley, Arthur, undated
- Connick, Harry Jr., 1997
- Contours, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 1)
- Covay, Don, undated
- Cooder, Ry, 1990, undated
- Cooke, Sam, undated
- Coolio, undated
- Cooper, Alice, undated
- Cope, Julian, circa 1989
- Corrs, undated
- Costello, Elvis, 1991-1998, undated
- Country Joe and the Fish, undated
- Cowsills, undated
- Cox, Ida, undated
- Cramer, Floyd, undated
- Cramps, undated
- Craving Theo, 2001
- Crawford, Hank, undated
- Cray, Robert, undated
- Cream, undated
- Creedence Clearwater Revival, undated
- Creeper Lagoon, 2001
- Crickets, undated
- Crosby, Bing, undated
- Crosby, Stills and Nash, undated
- Crosby, Stills, Nash, and Young, undated
- Crow, Sheryl, 1999, undated
- Crudup, Arthur, undated
- Cruz, Celia, undated
- Crystal Method, 2001
- Crystals, undated
- Cub Koda, 1993
- Cugat, Xavier, undated
- Cult, undated
- Custom, 2002
- Cure, undated
- D12, 2001
- D4L, undated
- Daashuur, Aja, undated
- Da Brat, 2000
- Daisy Theatre (Memphis, Tenn.), undated
- Dakona, undated
- Dale, Dick, undated
- Damita, 2000
- Damned, undated
- Daniels, Charlie, undated
- Danko, Rick, undated
- Danny and the Juniors, undated
- Darin, Bobby, 1960-1966, undated
- Darkness, undated
- Darling Buds, undated
- Dave Clark Five, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 2)
- David, Craig, undated
- Davies, Ray, undated
- Davis, Clive, 1999
- Davis, Reverend Gary, undated
- Davis, Guy, undated
- Davis, Miles, 1986-1992, undated
- Davis, Tyrone, undated
- Dawn, Laura, undated
- Days of the New, 2001
- Dazz Band, undated
- Dead Boys, circa 1976-1977, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 10-11)
  Exhibit History
  January-March 2012, Library & Archives, Raw Power: Researching the Evolution of Punk Rock (two b&w photos of a live performance)
- Dead Kennedys, undated
  January-March 2012, Library & Archives, Raw Power: Researching the Evolution of Punk Rock (b&w promo photo)
- Dead Milkmen, 1993
- Death Cab for Cutie, 2005
- Decemberists, 2007
- Deee-Lite, undated
- Deep Blue Something, 2001
- Deep Purple, undated
- Def Leppard, undated
- Deftones, 2003
- DeHory, Andrew, undated
- Del Amitri, undated
- Delaney and Bonnie, undated
- Dells, undated (Box OS2, Folder 1, Object 4)
- Delorme Brothers, undated
- Del Vikings, undated
- Denver, John, undated
- Deodato, undated
- Depeche Mode, undated
- Derailers, 2001
- Derek and the Dominos, undated
- Deshannon, Jackie, undated
- Destiny's Child, 2000-2001, undated
- Devo, undated
- Devotions, undated
- Dexy's Midnight Runners, undated
- Diamond, Neil, undated
- Die Krupps, undated
- DiFranco, Ani, undated
- Digable Planets, undated
- Digital Underground, 1998
- Dino, Desi and Billy, 1965
- Dion, 1998, undated
- Dion, Celine, undated
- Dire Straits, 1986-1993
- Dismemberment Plan, 1998
- Disney Music, undated
- Disturbed, 2002
- Ditty Bops, 2004
- Dixie Cups, undated
- Dixie Hummingbirds, undated
- Dixon, Willie, undated
- Dr. Dre, undated
- Domino, Fats, undated
- Dominoes, undated
- Donahue, Tom, 1976, 1996-1997
- Donnas
- Donovan, undated
- Doobie Brothers, undated
- Doors, 1967-1969, 1998, undated (Box OS2, Folder 1, Object 2)
- Dorsey, Lee, undated
- Dorsey, Thomas, undated
- Double Trouble, undated
- Dougan, Rob, 2002
- Douglas, Steve, undated
- Downing, Big Al, undated
- Drain STH, 1998
- Dramarama, undated
- Dream Syndicate, undated
- Drifters, 1960, undated
- D'Rivera, Paquito, undated
- Dropline, 2002
- Drown, undated
- DRS, 1993
- Du Droppers, undated
- Dunn, Donald "Duck", undated
  See Also
  Booker T. and the MGs
- Dupri, Jermaine, undated
- Duran Duran, 1983-1984
- Dwele, undated
- Dylan, Bob, 1972-2001, undated
- Eagles, undated
- Earshot, 2002
- Earth, Wind and Fire, undated
- Easton, undated
- Easy E, undated
- Eckstine, Billy, undated
- Edan, undated
- Eddy, Duane, undated
- Edge, Graeme, undated
- Edsels, undated
- Edwards, Bernard, undated
- Edwards, Honeyboy, undated
- Eels, 2001
- Einsturzende Neubaten, 1998
- Eisley, undated
- Eldorados, undated
- Electric Light Orchestra (ELO), undated
- Elliman, Yvonne, undated
- Ellington, Duke, undated
- Ely, Joe, undated
- Emerson, Lake and Palmer, 1970, undated
- Eminem, 1999-2000, undated
- Enchantment, undated
- Eno, Brian, undated
- Era, undated
- Erasure, undated
- Eric Gales Band, undated
- Ertegun, Ahmet, 1948-2006, undated (Box OS1, Folder 3)
- Ertegun, Nesuhi, undated
- E.S.T. (Esbjorn Svensson Trio), 2001-2002
- Eurogliders, undated
- Eva Trout, 1997
- Eve, 2001
- Everly Brothers, 1992-1993, undated (Box OS1, Folder 9, Object 3)
- Everly, Phil, undated (Box OS2, Folder 1, Object 3)
- Every Mother's Son, undated
- Evinrudes, 1998
- Exeter Group, undated
- Fabares, Shelley, 1964-1966
- Fabian, 1959-1965
- Fairfield Four, undated
- Fairport Convention, undated
- Faithfull, Marianne, undated
- Faith Healers, undated
- Fania All-Stars, undated
- Farner, Mark, undated
- Farrell, Joe, undated
- Farrell, Perry, 1991
- Faster Pussycat, undated
- Fayreweather, undated
- Fearing, Stephen, undated
- Feinstein, Michael, undated
- Felder, Don, undated
- Fender, Leo, undated
- Fenix-TX, undated
- Ferry, Bryan, undated
- Fiction Plane, undated
- Fighting Gravity, 1996-1998
- Filter, 2002
- Firstman, Joe, undated
- Fish, circa 1997
- Fitzgerald, Ella, 1938-1970, undated
- Five Keys, undated
- Five Royales, undated
- Five Stairsters, 1967
- Flamin' Groovies, undated
- Flaming Lips, 2002
- Flamingos, undated
- Flaw, undated
- Fleck, Bela and the Flecktones, 2001
- Fleetwood Mac, 1976-1988, undated
- Fleetwoods, undated
- Flestones, undated
- Floyd, Eddie, undated
- Fluid, 1993
- Flying Burrito Brothers, undated
- Flying Tigers, undated
- Fogelberg, Dan, undated
- Fogerty, John, undated
- Foghat, undated
- Foley, Ellen, undated
- Fondells, undated
- Fontana, D.J., undated
- Fontana, Wayne, undated
- Fontana, Wayne and the Mindbenders, undated
- Ford, Frankie, undated
- Ford, Willa, undated
- Foreigner, undated
- Fortran 5, undated
- Four Deuces, undated
- Four Seasons, undated
  General note
  Includes solo shots of Frankie Valli.
- Four Tops, undated
- Fourplay, undated
- Frames, undated
- Frampton, Peter, 1990, undated
- Francis, Connie, 1958-1965
- Franklin, Aretha, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 3)
- Franklin, Kirk, 1998
- Freddie and the Dreamers, undated
- Free, undated
- Freed, Alan, 1939-1959, undated (Box OS1, Folder 9, Object 4)
- Frisell, Bill, undated
- Front 242, 1991
- Frusciante, John, 2001
- Fuller, Jesse "The Lone Cat", undated
- Fulson, Lowell, undated
- Funeral for a Friend, undated
- Funicello, Annette, 1955-1965
- Furey, Lewis, undated
- Furtado, Nelly, 2000
- Fury, undated
- Gabe Dixon Band, 2001
- Gabriel, Peter, undated
- Gahan, Dave, 2003
- Galaie Brothers, undated
- Gale, Eric, undated
- Gales, Eric, 2001
- Gallagher, Rory, undated
- Gamble, Kenny, undated
- Gang of Four, 1982, undated
- Garbage, 1998-2001
- Garland, Judy, undated
- Garrett, Kenny, 2002
- Garrett, Leif, 1975-1978
- Garza, David, undated
- Gatton, Danny, undated
- Gaye, Marvin, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 4-5)
- Geiger, Teddy, 2005
- Genesis, undated
- Geraci, Sonny, 1993
- Gerry and the Pacemakers, undated
- Gershwin, George and Ira, undated
- Getz, Stan, undated
- Ghost of an American Airman, 1993
- Gibb, Andy, 1979-1980
- Gillespie, Dizzy, 1961, undated
- Gilmore, Jimmie Dale, 1992, undated
- Gilmour, David, undated
- Ginsberg, Arnie "Woo Woo", undated
- Girl group stamps, undated
- Gladiolas, undated
- Glassjaw, 2002
- Gleason, Ralph, undated
- Godsmack, undated
- God Street Wine, 1997
- Goffin, Jerry, and Carole King, 1963, undated
- Goffin, Louise, undated
- Gold, Alex, 2001
- Go-Gos, undated
- Golden Earring, undated
- Goldfinger, undated
- Goldsboro, Bobby, undated
- Goodman, Benny, 1955, undated
- Goo Goo Dolls, 2001-2002
- Gordon, Dexter, undated
- Gordy, Berry, 1964-2003, undated
- Gore, Lesley, 1963-1964, undated